Washingtoniana Slide Collection P026 P026
Test
- Series 5: Chamber of Commerce
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4239)
      Maynard Jackson and Andrew Young (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4240)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4241)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4242)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4243)
      Harry Belafonte (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4244)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4245)
      Alan Cranston (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4246)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4247)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4248)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4249)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4250)
      Walter Fauntroy (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4251)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4252)
      Gary Hart talking to male reporter (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4253)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4254)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4255)
      Gary Hart talking to male reporter in foreground, Ralph Abernathy on stage in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4256)
      Ossie Davis (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4257)
      Tony Bonilla and Walter Mondale (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4258)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4259)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4260)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4261)
      Walter Mondale shaking hands with crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4262)
      Reubin Askew laughing (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4263)
      Male and female performers (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4264)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4265)
      Tony Bonilla, Walter Mondale and unidentified male (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4266)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4267)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4268)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4269)
      Walter Mondale and two unidentified males (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4270)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4271)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4272)
      Walter Fauntroy talking to male reporter (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4273)
      Man in colorful clothing carrying paint and blowing bubbles, with Lincoln Memorial in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4274)
      Man in colorful clothing carrying paint and blowing bubbles (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4275)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4276)
      View of crowd in front of Lincoln Memorial (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4277)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27v (Item 4278)
      Crowd marching, holding signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4279)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4280)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4281)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4282)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4283)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4284)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4285)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4286)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4287)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4288)
      Jesse Jackson speaking to crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4289)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4290)
      Jesse Jackson in crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4291)
      Man with bullhorn (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4292)
      View of crowd in front of Capitol, from Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4293)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4294)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4295)
      View of crowd and stage, from Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4296)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4297)
      Marchers holding banner, "Mega Nation…from Minnesota" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4298)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4299)
      Marchers holding SCLC banner, "Working to fulfill the dream" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4300)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4301)
      Crowd holding signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4302)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4303)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4304)
      Woman on stage (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4305)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4306)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4307)
      Man on stage (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4308)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4309)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4310)
      Stacks of United Auto Workers signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4311)
      Crowd holding signs, Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4312)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4313)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4314)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4315)
      Man wading through pool (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4316)
      Young woman and man wading through pool (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4317)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4318)
      Maynard Jackson and Andrew Young (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4319)
      Andrew Young (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4320)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4321)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4322)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4323)
      People wading through pool, Lincoln Memorial in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4324)
      Children playing in pool, Lincoln Memorial in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4325)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue at 17th Street NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4326)
      People watching march from platform, marchers in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4327)
      Jesse Jackson and other leaders marching with crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4328)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4329)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4330)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4331)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4332)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4333)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4334)
      Jesse Jackson (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4335)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4336)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4337)
      Walter Fauntroy, Andrew Young seated in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4338)
      Martin Luther King, Sr. and grandchildren, Andrew Young seated in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4339)
      Young man at podium, Martin Luther Kings, Sr., grandchildren and Andrew Young in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4340)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4341)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4342)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4343)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4344)
      Alan Cranston talking to male reporter (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4345)
      Alan Cranston and other leaders among crowd (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4346)
      Stacks of UAW signs, Washington Monument in background (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4347)
      Man holding up LIFE magazine (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4348)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4349)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4350)
      Photographers on platform (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4351)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4352)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4353)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4354)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4355)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4356)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4357)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4358)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4359)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4360)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4361)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4362)
      Pete Seeger performing (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4363)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4364)
      Pete Seeger talking to male reporter (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4365)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4366)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4367)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4368)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4369)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4370)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4371)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4372)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4373)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4374)
      Man taking down banner from stage (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4375)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4376)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4377)
      Maya Angelou (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4378)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4379)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4380)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4381)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4382)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4383)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4384)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4385)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4386)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4387)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4388)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4389)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4390)
      Stacks of United Auto Workers signs (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4391)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4392)
      View of crowd with signs (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4393)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4394)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4395)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4396)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4397)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4398)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4399)
      Lights and vehicles in front of Lincoln Memorial (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4400)
      View of Lincoln Memorial from Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4401)
      People with banners, Lincoln Memorial in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4402)
      Woman lying under sign, "Nuclear Weaponry, the ultimate obscenity"; people with legs in pool, Lincoln Memorial in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4403)
      Crowd with Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4404)
      People wading through pool, with Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4405)
      People wading through pool, with Lincoln Memorial in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4406)
      Child sitting signs, Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4407)
      People with banner, "World peace through nuclear disarmament" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4408)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4409)
      Stacks of United Auto Workers signs, Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4410)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4411)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4412)
      Woman sitting with pile of paper; man taking down banner from stage in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4413)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4414)
      People sitting with banners, "Wimmin for womyn; Lesbian/feminists fighting for women's liberation" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4415)
      Sign on ground, "America's future is in the public schools" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Gardens Pond), 1983 August 27 (Item 4416)
      View from Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Gardens Pond), 1983 August 27 (Item 4417)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4418)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4419)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4420)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4421)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4422)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4423)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4424)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4425)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4426)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4427)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4428)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4429)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4430)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4431)
      Crowd with signs, Capitol in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4432)
      Crowd with signs, Capitol and Smithsonian Castle in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4433)